<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<!-- EN: The Shattered Empire, once a symbol of tyranny and oppression, has crumbled. All over the planet, brave deserters rose in a chorus of rebellion, breaking the chains of servitude that held them bound. Every child who now wakes to the dawn of freedom will remember and revere these names, the names of the heroes who dared to challenge the impossible:
{0}
\nHowever, this is not the end, but merely a transition. With the old empire now but ruins and their flagship a burning wreckage fallen from the skies, a time for healing and rebuilding is upon us. The nobles, once loyal to the empire, now surrender to outlander communities or lose themselves in a life of crime. There's no denying the truth - the world has forever changed.
\nAs you stand at the threshold of a new era, you remember this chapter of defiance and courage. The echoes of the Shattered Empire will serve as a reminder of your resilience, a testament to your unfaltering quest for freedom. You look ahead, knowing that you are stepping into a future built on hope, unity, and liberation. -->
<VFED.EndgameText>L'Empire, autrefois symbole de tyrannie et d'oppression, s'est effondré. Partout sur la planète, de courageux déserteurs se sont élevés dans un chœur de rébellion, brisant les chaînes de la servitude qui les retenaient. Chaque enfant qui s'éveille à l'aube de la liberté se souviendra de ces noms et les vénérera, les noms des héros qui ont osé défier l'impossible :\n{0}\n\nCependant, il ne s'agit pas d'une fin, mais d'une simple transition. L'ancien empire n'étant plus que ruines et son vaisseau amiral une épave en flammes tombée du ciel, le temps de la guérison et de la reconstruction est arrivé. Les nobles, autrefois fidèles à l'empire, se soumettent désormais aux communautés d'étrangers ou se perdent dans la criminalité. On ne peut nier la vérité : le monde a changé à jamais.\n\nAlors que vous vous trouvez au seuil d'une nouvelle ère, vous vous souvenez de ce chapitre de défi et de courage. Les échos de l'Empire vous rappelleront votre résilience et témoigneront de votre quête inébranlable de liberté. Vous regardez vers l'avenir, sachant que vous entrez dans un futur construit sur l'espoir, l'unité et la libération.</VFED.EndgameText>
<!-- EN: You are about to initiate a final mission in Vanilla Factions Expanded: Deserters. After the mission is complete, the Empire and the Deserters will be no more. Are you sure you want to initiate the final mission? -->
<VFED.EndgameWarningText>Vous êtes sur le point de lancer la mission finale dans Vanilla Factions Expanded : Deserters. Une fois la mission terminée, l'Empire et les Déserteurs n'existeront plus. Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir commencer la mission finale ?</VFED.EndgameWarningText>


</LanguageData>