<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<!-- EN: uhlan -->
<VREH_Uhlan.label>uhlan</VREH_Uhlan.label>
<!-- EN: Uhlans are a side-development from captured hussars, turned by certain elements to become a counter to the military-developed supersoldier programs. Their genetic dependence on luciferium is both a deterrent against capturing and an improvement to long-term usefulness.\n\nAppropriately named demons for their permanently flushed skin and intense bloodthirst, uhlans are incredibly resilient and specialized in certain styles of combat. Quite often they are decked out in heavy armor, in which they can charge full tilt at their intended target.\n\nExtremely specialized and on a permanent hair-trigger, there has been much speculation that their development was sponsored by megacorporations as part of the latest arms race. No substantial evidence has been presented to support these claims. -->
<VREH_Uhlan.description>Les uhlans sont une évolution secondaire des hussards capturés, transformés par certains éléments pour contrer les programmes de supersoldats développés par l'armée. Leur dépendance génétique au luciferium est à la fois un moyen de dissuasion contre la capture et une amélioration de leur utilité à long terme.\n\nAppelés à juste titre démons pour leur peau rougie en permanence et leur soif de sang intense, les uhlans sont incroyablement résistants et spécialisés dans certains styles de combat. Très souvent, ils sont équipés d'une armure lourde qui leur permet de foncer sur leur cible.\n\nExtrêmement spécialisés et sur le qui-vive en permanence, on a beaucoup spéculé sur le fait que leur développement a été parrainé par des méga-corporations dans le cadre de la dernière course à l'armement. Aucune preuve substantielle n'a été présentée pour soutenir ces affirmations.</VREH_Uhlan.description>
<!-- EN: Uhlans are engineered super-soldiers who fight aggressively and without emotion. They heal extremely fast, glide through obstacles using their small wings, freely ingest military drugs and rely on luciferium to keep their bodies functioning. -->
<VREH_Uhlan.descriptionShort>Les Uhlans sont des super-soldats modifiés qui se battent de manière agressive et sans émotion. Ils guérissent extrêmement vite, glissent à travers les obstacles grâce à leurs petites ailes, consomment librement des drogues militaires et dépendent du luciferium pour faire fonctionner leur corps.</VREH_Uhlan.descriptionShort>


</LanguageData>